<emails><!--Copy here--><email><subject>skate park</subject><from>Volcano Island Skaters Club</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">Dear Mayor:  We still don't have a skate park. Would you spend two coins to build a skate park? It will help your popularity with the skaters. Want to go ahead? </body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="3" popularity="1" preparation="0"><from>Volcano Island Skaters Club</from><body>Dear Mayor: We're so grateful for the  skate park. Since it opened, we've noticed that tourism on the island has gone up, bringing in more than enough coins to pay back the cost of building the park. Thank you!</body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="-1" preparation="0"><from>Volcano Island Skaters Club</from><body>Dear Mayor:  We are disappointed that you decided not to build the park. We hope you'll reconsider if this comes up again. Until later.</body></replyNo></email><email><subject>Minister of Tourism</subject><from>CPI (Citizens for a Peaceful Island)</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">Dear Mayor: Party Cruise Lines wants to stop at the island. This will make the island crowded on those days, but will bring in much needed income. What shall I tell them? Want to go ahead? </body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="-1" preparation="0"><from>From: CPI (Citizens for a Peaceful Island)</from><body>Mayor, Whenever those boatloads full of tourists dock here, the streets get so crowded, we can't get around. We are angry and upset that you did not consult with us first even though we do like the extra money. Bye. </body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="0" preparation="0"><from>From: Volcano Souvenirs Inc.</from><body>Dear Mayor: We are sorry that you decided not to let the extra tourists come here on weekends. We hope you will reconsider if this comes up again. Thank you</body></replyNo></email><email><subject>Beach party?</subject><from>Social Director</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">Mayor: Our town is long overdue for a social event. You can raise your popularity by calling for a beach party and it will only cost you two coins! Want to go ahead? Choose</body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="-2" popularity="2" preparation="0"><from>Happy Citizens</from><body>Hi Mayor: This party is a BLAST! We are so grateful you finally did something to break the monotony around here.</body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="-1" preparation="0"><from>Test Social Director</from><body>Mayor: The townspeople are grumbling ever since you turned down their beach party request. Do you think you might need to watch your popularity?</body></replyNo></email><email><subject>Town barbeque????</subject><from>Social Director</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">People in town really enjoyed the Volcano Island barbeque last year. Would you be willing to set aside two coins to make sure that we have one this year?</body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="-2" popularity="1" preparation="0"><from>Town Treasurer</from><body>Dear Mayor: Great, I'm glad that I will be able to bring the family to the barbeque this year. By the way, the town bank account has been charged two coins.</body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="-2" preparation="0"><from>Unhappy Citizen </from><body>Dear Mayor, I think it is a shame about the barbeque. I hope if this comes up again, you will reconsider.</body></replyNo></email><email><subject>Gift to town?</subject><from>Wealthy Townsperson</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">My friend, I have lived in Volcano Island all my life, and I would like to give back to the town. Would you accept a gift of two coins from my personal fortune toward a rainy day fund in case the town has to be evacuated?</body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="2" popularity="1" preparation="0"><from>Wealthy Townsperson</from><body>Thank you for accepting my gift. The townspeople are happier knowing that the town is saving money to pay for a possible evacuation. </body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="-1" popularity="-2" preparation="-1"><from>Wealthy Townsperson</from><body>The townspeople are getting worried that you turned down my offer to help pay for an evacuation. I hope if this comes up again, you will reconsider.</body></replyNo></email><email><subject>Town Parade</subject><from>Social Director</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">Dear Mayor:It has been a while since we had a parade. Would you allow us to organize one?  It will cost two coins, but will help your popularity a lot! Thanks!</body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="-2" popularity="2" preparation="0"><from>Social Director</from><body>Dear Mayor:Thanks for the parade! It was a blast. People are much happier now.</body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="-2" preparation="0"><from>Social Director</from><body>Dear Mayor:People are really disappointed that they didn't get a parade. You might want to look at your popularity. No one will listen to you if you call for an evacuation warning if your popularity gets too low. </body></replyNo></email><email><subject>Statue is missing!</subject><from>Chief of Police</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">Mayor --- Last night our beautiful statue was stolen from the town square. People are looking at the hole where it once was and are losing confidence in the government. Should we increase police patrols?</body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="-1" popularity="1" preparation="0"><from>Chief of Police</from><body>Mayor --- People are glad you decided to increase police patrols. It will cost money, but at least your Popularity will start to go up again. </body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="-1" popularity="-2" preparation="0"><from>Chief of Police</from><body>Mayor -- People are wondering what will be stolen next? Are we in a crime wave? Some businesses will have to close early, and that will decrease town revenues. </body></replyNo></email><email><subject>Statue is missing!</subject><from>Chief of Police</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">Mayor --- Last night, the statue of our founder disappeared from the town square. Should we replace it?</body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="-2" popularity="1" preparation="0"><from>Chief of Police</from><body>Mayor -- People are glad you decided to replace the statue. They are confident the town is on the right track.</body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="-2" preparation="0"><from>Chief of Police</from><body>Mayor -- People are worried about the crime wave in their town and are looking forward to the next election so they can vote for a change in leadership. Business is down so revenues are down too.</body></replyNo></email><email><subject>Free advice</subject><from>Ex-Mayor of Volcano Island</from><body yesBtn="yes" noBtn="no">Dear Sir/Madam, I know that you probably do not want to hear from me, but I suggest you check out the Mayors Handbook! Did you know you raise preparation by looking at it?</body><replyYes doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="0" preparation="1"><from>Ex-Mayor of Volcano Island</from><body>Yes, looking at the handbook helps you be a better mayor!</body></replyYes><replyNo doneBtn="done" money="0" popularity="-1" preparation="-1"><from>Ex-Mayor of Volcano Island</from><body>I didn't look at the handbook, and look what happened to me...voted out of office!</body></replyNo></email><!--Start after warning messages here--></emails>