<QA>
<question>
What is a seismometer?
</question>
<answer>
A seismometer is a device that records vibrations in the Earth – earthquakes. They produce seismographs, like the one on the screen in your office. The squiggly lines on the graph tell you that earthquakes, some quite small, are happening at the volcano.  The bigger the vibrations, the bigger the squiggles are on the graph. When a volcano is about to erupt, magma moves upward and reaches the cold, brittle rock at the surface. This magma cracks and breaks the rock as it tries to escape.  Seismometers record the earthquakes that occur as this happens.  Some of the earthquakes are so small they can’t be felt by a person, only by a seismometer. Right before an eruption, there are often swarms of small earthquakes. If you begin to see that earthquakes are getting more frequent and more intense, then you might want to send out a warning.  Of course, there are sometimes false alarms – when the ground shakes and the seismometers go crazy, but there is no volcanic eruption. Earthscope has deployed seismometers across the North American continent.
</answer>
<question>
How is GPS used to monitor a volcano?
</question>
<answer>
The Global Positioning System, or GPS, is one tool that scientists use to predict when an eruption might be coming. A GPS receiver is used to calculate exact locations using radio signals from satellites. You might have used GPS to keep from getting lost while on hikes on in your car. An even more sensitive GPS station mounted on the Earth tells geoscientists how much the Earth is moving – even if it’s only by a few millimeters. GPS stations installed by EarthScope and other programs are placed strategically around a volcano to sense ground movement, which is then analyzed by a computer.
On the GPS computer monitor, the line shows how much the surface near the volcano is moving up or down. If the ground under the volcano starts swelling upward, the likelihood of an eruption gets greater!
</answer>
</QA>