<QA>
<question>
What is a volcano?
</question>
<answer>
The word volcano is used to describe a place in the Earth’s crust where hot, melted rock (magma) and gases escape from below the surface.  The word volcano is also used to describe the feature that is formed as erupted materials from this opening build up (over many years) in many layers to form a mountain.  The erupted material can include lava, ash flows, airborne ash and dust, and volcanic bombs (blobs of lava that cool into solid fragments before they even hit the ground. 
</answer>
<question>
What is magma?  And what is lava?
</question>
<answer>
Magma is rock under the surface of the earth that has been heated up so much that it flows (just like if you heat chocolate, it flows!).  Most magma is formed from rocks heated by the friction of plate tectonics (in the same way that rubbing your hands together quickly makes them feel warm).  Plate tectonics is the process where large pieces of the Earth’s crust are moving slowly in relation to each other.  

After magma is erupted by a volcano, it becomes known as lava.  In other words, this melted rock is “magma” underground and “lava” after it has reached the surface.  

</answer>
<question>
What causes volcanoes to erupt?
</question>
<answer>
When solid rock is heated to become magma, it becomes less dense than the surrounding solid rock and so it tries to rise to the surface (a bit like the way a balloon pushed under water will try to push back to the surface of the water – the air inside it makes the balloon less dense than the water).  The magma will keep on rising to the surface unless it reaches a barrier of solid rock that is strong enough to stop it.  If this happens, the magma will keep on building up, just under the surface of the earth, in what scientists call a magma chamber.  Sometimes the magma keeps building up in the magma chamber until the pressure gets so great that it breaks through the solid rock barrier as a dramatic eruption.  Other times, the magma will escape more slowly, as lava flowing down the side of the volcano. 
</answer>
<question>
How are active, dormant and extinct volcanoes different from one another?
</question>
<answer>An active volcano is a volcano that is erupting, or likely to erupt again (dormant).  A volcano can be dormant for long periods of time; some people define an active volcano as one that has had at least one eruption during the past 10,000 years.

An extinct volcano is one that scientists consider unlikely to erupt again, because the volcano no longer has a lava supply.  Sometimes it is hard to tell whether a volcano is dormant or extinct.
</answer>
<question>
What could happen if the volcano erupts?
</question>
<answer>
An active volcanic eruption can be dangerous to people nearby. Volcanic eruptions might include lava flows, ash, mudslides, hot rocks shooting through the air, and even poison gas.
</answer>
<question>
How will I know if or when the volcano is going to erupt?
</question>
<answer>
When living with a volcano, it’s important to constantly monitor it, so that people can be evacuated in time. Scientists use seismometers and GPS receivers, like those in the <font color="#336699"><a>EarthScope</a></font> network, to monitor volcano behavior These instruments will help you predict eruptions. The two screens in your office show the up-to-minute data gathered by these instruments.
</answer>


</QA>